Kurgan the Crafty: Warriors! Today I will address you all.
Kurgan the Crafty: We've been waiting for a long time. We believed!
Kurgan the Crafty: And he came.
Kurgan the Crafty: He made us rich.
Kurgan the Crafty: He defeated the most powerful enemies.
Kurgan the Crafty: he's proven he's stronger than Uro-Boros!
Kurgan the Crafty: He is Skulnar the Fierce, the reborn Legendary Orc and our leader! Chief, a speech for your people!
Skulnar the Fierce: Ugh... Strength and freedom!
Landfill Warriors: Chief! Freedom and strength! Freedom and strength!
Fury the Fierce: ...And the Hero of Sarnaut is a new friend of our people!
Landfill Warriors: Eh... and the Hero of Sarnaut! Freedom and strength!
Landfill Warriors: Freedom and strength! Freedom and strength! Freedom and strength!